Guide to the James Alport Donovan, Jr. Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, Accession 2017-M-0055
  - Course notes, 1933-1940
    - German notebook, Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Goethe, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Gothic, Circa 1938 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - History of German, Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Hittite, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Hittite, Comparative German, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Introductory Linguistics, Circa 1938 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Language Dissertations, published by the Linguistic Society of America, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Latin Vocabulary, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Old Icelandic, Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Phonetics, Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Sanskrit, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Sanskrit Reader, by Charles Rockwell Lanman, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Memorabilia and correspondence, 1939-1981
    - 1939-1953, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Includes newspaper clippings, correspondence, and Coast Guard pamphlets.
    - Letters from James Donovan, Jr. to Robert Thomson and Hazel Boltwood, 1966-01-10-1966-03-30 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Includes biographical note from Katherine Donovan.
    - Family, Alexandria, VA, 1977, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Includes school pamphlets, parchment replicas, cards, and newspaper clippings.
    - Two photographs of Lyndon Baines Johnson and unidentified people, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Samuel Butler Newsletter
      - Correspondence, 1961-1979, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Material for future issues, 1962-1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Papers for Donovan family, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Volumes I-III, complete set, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Copies of Newsletter, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Published materials, 1891-1968
    - Bible, New Testament, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Ekkehard. Eine Geschichte aus dem zehnten Jahrhundert, by Joseph Victor von Scheffel, 1891 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - L'exode des Chervaux, by Walter Adams and Henri Rieben, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Contains facsimiles of cover, title page, and annotated page.
    - Sinclair Lewis, by Hans Kriesi, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Contains facsimiles of cover, title page, and newspaper clippings.